(faint crickets chirping)
(wind whistling)
(soft rock music)
♪ Well, there's a black
man with a black cat ♪
♪ Livin' in a black neighborhood ♪
♪ He's got an interstate
runnin' through his front yard ♪
♪ You know he thinks that
he's got it so good ♪
♪ And there's a woman in the kitchen ♪
♪ Cleanin' up the evening slop ♪
♪ And he looks at her
and says, hey, darlin' ♪
♪ I can remember when
you could stop a clock ♪
♪ Oh, but ain't that America ♪
♪ For you and me ♪
♪ Ain't that America ♪
♪ Something to see, baby ♪
♪ Home of the free, yeah ♪
♪ Little pink houses for you and me ♪
♪ Ooh, yeah ♪
♪ For you and me ♪
♪ Well, there's a young man in a T-shirt ♪
♪ Listenin' to a rockin' rollin' station ♪
♪ He's got greasy hair, greasy smile ♪
♪ He says, Lord this
must be my destination ♪
♪ 'Cause they told me when I was younger ♪
♪ Said, boy, you're gonna be president" ♪
♪ But just like everything else ♪
♪ Those old crazy dreams
just kinda came and went ♪
♪ Oh, but ain't that America ♪
♪ For you and me ♪
♪ Ain't that America ♪
♪ Something to see, baby ♪
♪ Home of the free, yeah ♪
♪ Little pink houses for you and me ♪
♪ Oh, little baby, for you and me ♪
♪ Well, there's people and more people ♪
♪ What do they know, know, know ♪
♪ Go to work in some high-rise ♪
♪ And vacation down at
the Gulf of Mexico ♪
♪ Ooh, yeah ♪
♪ And there's winners and there's losers ♪
♪ But they ain't no big deal ♪
♪ 'Cause the simple man,
baby, pays for thrills ♪
♪ The bills, the pills that kill ♪
♪ Oh, but ain't that America ♪
♪ For you and me ♪
♪ Ain't that America ♪
♪ Something to see, baby ♪
♪ Home of the free, yeah ♪
♪ Little pink houses for you and me ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Ooh, yeah ♪
♪ Ain't that America ♪
♪ For you and me ♪
♪ Hey, something to see, baby ♪
♪ Ain't that America ♪
♪ Oh, the home of the free ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Little pink houses,
baby, for you and me ♪
♪ Ooh, yeah ♪